Office of Academic Affairs Records
Archives and Special Collections at the SUNY Upstate Health Sciences Library
Office of Academic Affairs Records
1972-2011
SUNY Upstate Medical University 766 Irving Avenue Syracuse, NY 13210
Upstate Medical University (N.Y.) Office of Academic Affairs
7.5 linear ft.
This collection consists of records produced by the Office of Academic Affairs at SUNY Upstate Medical University. Currently, there is one series within the collection consisting of accreditation materials. Additional materials will be added over time.
2014.0004, 2021.0008
Historical Note
The Office of Academic affairs works behind the scenes with the president, vice presidents, deans, faculty and staff across the colleges to support university accreditation, institutional and strategic planning regarding education, and individual educational program development and approval process through SUNY and the New York Office of Education. The Office also supports academic policy development and revision, the measurement of student learning outcomes and evaluation of educational programs, honorary degrees, and various faculty awards.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
Records in this collection were produced by the Office of Academic Affairs. There is currently one series on accreditation.
Accreditation: this series includes materials relating to LCME and Middle States studies conducted at Upstate Medical University from 1972 through 2011. Consists mostly of reports and meeting minutes.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection currently has one series that is arranged chronologically within each subseries.
Subject and Genre Headings
SUNY Upstate Medical University; Universities and colleges--Departments; Accreditation (Education); Syracuse,(N.Y.)
Access Restrictions
These materials are restricted to use by the University only. Permission to access records must be granted by the Office of Academic Affairs.
Inventory
- Accreditation
  - LCME, 1978 (Box Box 1)
  - LCME, 1978 (Box Box 2)
  - LCME, 1981-1983 (Box Box 3)
  - LCME, 1987-1988 (Box Box 4)
  - LCME, 1988 (Box Box 5)
  - LCME, 1988-1989 (Box Box 6)
  - LCME, 1989 (Box Box 7)
  - LCME, 1989 (Box Box 8)
  - LCME, 1989 (Box Box 9)
  - LCME, 1989 (Box Box 10)
  - LCME, 1990 (Box Box 11)
  - LCME, 1992-1994 (Box Box 12)
  - LCME, 1995 (Box Box 13)
  - LCME, 1996 (Box Box 14)
  - LCME, 1996 (Box Box 15)
  - LCME, 1996 (Box Box 16)
  - LCME, 2000-2003 (Box Box 17)
  - LCME, 2002-2003 (Box Box 18)
  - LCME, 2010-2011 (Box Box 19)
  - Middle States, 1972-1999 (Box Box 20)
  - Middle States, 1997-1999 (Box Box 21)
  - Middle States, 2004-2009 (Box Box 22)